this is it
your power has grown to preposterous levels
your chemical storage is overflowing
your blast furnace has been running for days
you're swimming in stainless steel
but now you need to become multi planetary
the vacuum of space is lethal to the unprepared
but that's why you're here
it's time for the home stretch
you're on the precipice of the midgame
ready to move on from this beginner stuff
so today we go to space
this is episode 8
HV
to Infinity and beyond
MV was a pretty straight line
a nice little self-contained chapter
HV is the opposite
you're gonna be jumping around in the quest book quite a bit
you should have the habits down by now
so start with the you're gonna hate this quests
just a reminder
in every tier you'll have a bunch of new stuff to do
but also some of the same stuff every time
make machine parts
upgrade machines
make energy hatches
make coils
make plastics
and improve circuits
sometimes the order is varied up
sometimes you can put things off for a long time
but eventually you'll do it all
assuming you have all the stainless steel you need
and don't forget about mining the basics
especially copper
nothing's really stopping you from going straight at it
you can get the MV circuit assembler right away
and start making circuits faster
you won't be able to make any of the new circuits until you get the clean room though
we'll get to that
for now take advantage of the speed
and grab some important upgrades
the HV miners are super worth having
and the last stop before you can get into the multi block mining rigs
grab 3 or 4
and keep them running on everything all the time
and grab compressed chests too
they're pricey
but they keep their inventory when broken
so this is a massive upgrade for your mining process
HV machines also add an output slot
so you can start getting by product bonus outputs from various ore processing stages
not every byproduct is worth having
some just gum up the works
so filtering and fully automating processing at this point can be awkward if you don't know some magic
with a couple of macerators, ore washers and centrifuges
you can stay loaded with resources
copper especially is nice for all the bonus gold
but tons of stuff is worth running through
starting your nickel through the macerator
then sending it through a chemical bath with mercury
will net you a fair amount of early platinum too
you should upgrade all your workshop machines
but until your passive setups for chemicals and silicone
and everything else you set up are too slow
there's no need to upgrade those
you'll just run into a power crunch sooner than you otherwise would have
at this point
the main things that are going to be eating power are the EBF and the ore processing line you just set up
use all the fuel you have keeping those going
and if you have extra, power your workshop
if not this is a good time to make use of your old steam infrastructure
and send a drip of power to a battery for your hand use machines
having to wait for batteries to charge to use single blocks is a little annoying
but losing time redoing failed smelting operations in the EBF is worse
if you find yourself waiting more than you can stand
it's time to scale up your power production
if your power is holding up well
skip ahead to the clean room
but you'll want to hear what's next either way
if you went oil for power
and frankly, even if you didn't
you might want to think about an oil drilling rig
and some long distance piping
use your prospector on bedrock
and find a fluid pool of regular oil
the underground pools are giant
so you should be safe to pump here for a long while
pop down the multi block oil rig
attach a long distance pipe input
load the chunk
and place pipes down until you get back to your base
and when you get back
send the oil into your new distillation tower
this multi block has a bunch of options for configuration
to figure out which one you need
you need to know which recipe you're using
to start with distillation
you can distill oil at MV which gives four outputs
as the tool tip suggests
you can only have one fluid output per layer
and an item output needs to be in the bottom layer
so the tower needs to be five blocks tall
easy enough right
just like the single block
the outputs are contaminated with sulfur
and you'll have to mix them with hydrogen to get the clean output
if you use a multi block chemical reactor with five input hatches
one for each oil product and one for hydrogen
and two output hatches
you can easily desulfurize everything in just one machine
you'll probably need a dedicated hydrogen production
and be sure to save the hydrogen sulfide to turn into sulfuric acid later
you're gonna need every drop of the stuff you can get coming up very soon
once you got the clean outputs
it's time to decide what to do with them
here's what I suggest as a starting point
mix the light fuel and heavy fuel to get diesel
you either just got a supplementary fuel source
or you upgraded your existing one
send the naptha into a multi block oil cracker
lightly steam crack it
and then send that into a max size distillation tower
the 12 tall behemoth with 11 fluid outputs
and super tanks for everything
every last chemical is useful
and some will be critical shortly
as for the refinery gas
you can steam crack that as well and distill it in a 6 tall tower
but for the moment
if you just want to use a single block distillery
and crank out ethylene to make your polyethylene setup a bit better
I wouldn't be mad at you
you'll also get ethylene from the naphtha to set up
so you should be all set
if you go with all single blocks
other than the crackers and distillation towers
it'll end up looking something like this once you finish the whole line
by turning the fuel into cetane boosted diesel
huge mess right
so let's circle back to the LCR
you're going to be making a lot of these
so no time like the present start using them
you'll need the HV tier plastic
polytetrafluoroethylene
this is a minor little resource check in the quest book
you'll need decent supplies of fluorine and chlorine
and neither of those are as straightforward to get as the standard gases
if you haven't gotten into bees or IC2 crops
your best bet is to electrolyze cryolite for fluorine and salt for chlorine
the good news is
you really only need this stuff for LCR's for now
the main reason you want to get into these right away
is you can send multiple fluids into them to react
that's right no more cell management
at least for chemical reactors
the gods rejoice
these things can fit tons of input and output hatches
and the outputs can be filtered
just remember to mind the recipes tier
and be smart about how much power you supply
next up, you can start cooking some new boules
to get the phosphorus
you can break down tricalcium phosphate
grabbable at apatite vein in the overworld
you'll also need nitrogen in the EBF
which you can get from cell cycling compressed air cells into a centrifuge
once again
this is a long smelt
good thing you just upgraded your fuel
these aren't a hard requirement
other than to complete the quest
but like with the other circuit components
your resources go further the better the input is
while the boules cook
it's time to start preparing for the clean room
the quest book does a good job explaining how it works
so to summarize briefly
build a 5 by 5 by 5 box
put the controller in the top middle
surround it with filter machine casings
and make the rest out of plascrete blocks
toss down an LV Energy hatch
a maintenance hatch
and a way in
and the last thing you absolutely need is the cable diode
and the 4 amp MV diode will work just fine to begin
stick the diode in a wall
and run the right amount of power in
as the quest book suggests
you need to give the cleanroom 40 EU per tick
so two LV generators will do the job
you probably remember from dealing with the EBF
that an energy hatch can take 2 amps of power
so send power from both right on in
and don't forget to send the power into the diode too
do some maintenance
then pop on in and turn the cleaner on
if all is well
you'll see it starts working
and very slowly increases the efficiency by one percent at a time
anything less than 100% efficiency
and you might void an item
and if it happens to be a mainframe circuit
you're gonna have a bad time
opening the door to the clean room lowers the efficiency
so replace it with an elevator or a travel anchor
and act like you never made it
run some cable from the diode
and plop down the cutting machine, laser engraver and the circuit assembler
you'll need HV power in the clean room very soon
but for the moment
you're gaming
if you figured out chlorine enough to get the polytetra
hopefully you have some spare for a massive batch of iron III chloride
you were able to put off the circuit boards last episode
but not anymore
aside from just the chlorine
you're about to use the most insane quantity of copper that you have ever seen required by modded Minecraft
at least so far
be sure to use the best recipes you can afford
and if you think you have enough circuit supplies
you don't
it might take an entire day to accumulate enough stuff here
start with eight stacks of boards
but be ready for eight more behind that
the circuit quantities are about to explode
to make the single IV mainframe you need for the quest
you'll need 14 plastic boards
it escalates quickly from here
on the bright side
you can make ULV, LV and MV circuits in a single step now
and for as cheap as they're gonna get
stock up on LV circuits
you'll need them
and once you've worked your way up to the EV circuit
which by the way use a fluid extractor, fluid solidifier combination for the blue alloy bolts
you'll thank yourself
you can make the vacuum freezer
which you should do as a priority
no more silly coolant cooling
and no better time either
because you've just realized how important those cheaper circuit components are
and you want to cook copious volumes of tantalum you've just extracted from the nether with your shiny new miners
so add an HV diode, an HV generator and the HV circuit assembler
and make your first IV circuits
my God they're pricey
and go ahead and make the NASA workbench too
it'll make you feel good to have it
however briefly
you can grab the implosion compressor now as well
at this point an easy craft
the problem is you need explosives
I'm going to take this as another opportunity to encourage getting into bees
because staying in supply of iTNT without them is going to be a little bit more complicated
another shameless plug of Aditya's bees guide
watch them, use them
hold them in highest esteem
in case that doesn't interest you at all
here's your alternatives
more setups for hydrogen oxygen and nitrogen
being used to make ammonia
nitrogen oxide
nitrogen dioxide
and then nitric acid
it's still a bit early to centralize fluids easily
but you'll need these chemicals again for the cetane-boosted diesel
so keep that in mind
you can probably share at least this setup if you're smart
if you're mixing sulfuric acid from the hydrogen sulfide you're getting from the oil line
route some over here and combine it with a nitric acid
otherwise divert some oxygen from your local setup
and mix some fresh on site to combine with a nitric acid for a nitration mixture
and use the LCR recipe, it's easier
you got the toluene from distilling naphtha
so send it through a ball mold in the fluid sterilizer for gelled toluene
if you're set up for it
you get better returns on the toluene using sugar and polyethylene
but when's the last time you checked on your farms
do bees really seem that bad to do now
it's not getting any better from here
trust me
after you have a couple dozen stacks of iTNT or so
you can make compressed plates
you're going to use an insane amount of resources here
if you follow the order of the god
this represents days and days of effort and smelting and crafting
the videos have been snappy
but don't mistake that for progress being fast
as usual the quest book does an excellent job of laying out the steps
you need most of the stuff here
slowly but surely make your way towards the rocket
the tier 1 lander
the oxygen gear
and the launch equipment
and when you have it all
you'll need to gas up the beast
you have two choices
cetane-boosted diesel or RP1 rocket fuel
and cetane is going to be pretty easy if you follow it along pretty closely
you've got nitric acid and sulfuric acid standing by for making TNT
and extra ethylene from distilling naphtha
you can mix with oxygen for acetic acid
the last chemical you need to get ethenone
and ultimately tetranitromethane once you react it with the nitric acid
mix that with a bit of fuel
and you're ready for space flight
if you can automate this whole process
this is a pretty big upgrade from regular fuel for your base too
snag up that space gear
and it's time for final checks
and be sure you make them
go ahead and fill your oxygen
you'll notice that the galacticraft blocks are sided
so make sure the energy is actually going in
and the oxygen is actually coming out on the collector
and that both are going in on the compressor
goofy little blocks
and don't forget to bring them with you
then it's confirming:
oxygen, tanks, miners, compressed chests, generators, fuel, leaves, a fuel loader, glowstone torches, EnderIO capacitor and energy conduits
check check check
you can collect oxygen on the moon too
that's why you're bringing the stack of leaves
just cut out a cave
line them with leaves
and plop the collector down
the more leaves close by the better
and with that
you're ready to launch
don't forget anything
mission control
this is flycorand (?)
we have impact
no time to waste
slay monsters and light the night if you need to
otherwise get right to work prospecting
and looking around for the dungeon entrance
basically just a big hole in the ground
and you can see bricks at the bottom of it
you're looking for neodymium, bauxite, ilmenite, chromite and aluminum
tons of goodies here to supply life on earth
get your miners out. get them set, and get them chunk loaded
then go boss hunting
even if you can't fly
you can really just zip right through the dungeon straight to the boss arena
and kill the boss very very easily
grab the key, check the chest
and cross your fingers for a tier 2 rocket template
eh
if you don't get one
find more dungeons and kill more bosses until you do
it won't take long
once you're content with your haul, head on home
don't feel bad about making a home location on the moon either
no one's judging you because no one knows you did it
and all that's left now
is processing the aluminate and bauxite into rutile
full on maxing out the production is going to be worth it here
so macerate the bauxite ore down to crush form
then send it through a chemical bath with sodium persulfate
you can expand on this by processing the purified boxite into boxite slurry
and investing in the full bauxite line
we ain't going to cover it now, but look it up
insane returns, insane
you can do some similar things with the ilmenite too
except using sulfuric acid
for insane returns on rutile
and a closed loop for getting the sulfuric acid back
but not until EV
if you're desperate
you can run ilmenite through the full
macerator-washer-macerator-centrifuge line
for some bonus rutile
but you're probably better off just getting more bauxite
once you're all set on rutile
you can start converting it into titanium
the quest book explains it
but in short
the whole processing line is a giant closed loop
where the only input is rutile
to kick start it
you need chlorine and carbon to go with the rutile at an LCR
electrolyze the resulting carbon monoxide
send the titanium chloride to the EBF with magnesium
cool the resulting hot titanium
and send the magnesium chloride to a chemical reactor to combine with sodium for the magnesium back
and some salt which you can electrolyze for your original chlorine and the sodium you just used
all it takes is a little logistics
and it can run as long as you stay in rutile
and you're gonna want to run it for a long long time
you've done it
you're out of the early game
you're officially no longer a beginner
just in time for new beginnings
this is GTNH after all
the learning is never done
there's a lot more to do in HV too
but you know how to look around now
Applied Energetics is on the horizon
if you can get enough titanium that is
hopefully this guide sets you up with enough information to take a real crack at the pack
you won't regret it
see you in the game
and hey stay positive out there
这就是了
你的力量已经发展到荒谬的程度了
你的化学药品储藏室快溢出来了
你的高炉已经运行了好几天了
你在不锈钢里游泳
但现在你需要成为多行星
太空的真空对毫无准备的人是致命的
但这就是你来这里的原因
到最后冲刺的时间了
你正处于比赛中期的边缘
准备好从初学者的东西继续前进
所以今天我们去太空
这是第八集
高压
到无限和超越
MV是条直线
一个漂亮的小独立章节
HV则相反
你会在任务书里跳来跳去的
你现在应该改掉这些习惯了
所以从你会讨厌这个任务开始
只是提醒一下
每层都有很多新东西要做
但每次都有一些相同的东西
制造机器零件
升级机器
制造能量舱口
制作线圈
制造塑料
并改进电路
有时顺序会发生变化
有时候你可以把事情拖很久
但最终你会做到一切
假设你有你需要的所有不锈钢
不要忘记挖掘基础知识
尤其是铜
没有什么能阻止你直奔主题
您可以立即获得MV电路汇编器
并开始更快地制作电路
在你得到洁净室之前你不能做任何新电路
我们会谈到这一点的
现在利用速度
并获得一些重要的升级
高压矿工超级值得拥有
也是进入多区块采矿平台之前的最后一站
抓住3或4
让他们一直在所有事情上运行
并抓住压缩的胸部
它们很贵。
但他们在损坏时保留库存
所以这是对您的采矿过程的巨大升级
高压机器还增加了一个输出插槽
因此，您可以开始从不同的矿石加工阶段获得产品奖励输出
不是每个副产品都值得拥有
有些人只是把工作搞砸了
因此，如果您不知道一些魔法，此时的过滤和完全自动化处理可能会很尴尬
有几台浸渍机、洗矿机和离心机
您可以保持资源负载
铜尤其适合所有额外的黄金
但是很多东西都值得一试
通过浸渍器启动你的镍
然后用水银把它送入化学浴
也会为你净赚相当多的早期白金
你应该升级你所有的车间机器
但直到你的化学物质和硅胶的被动设置
而且你设置的其他东西都太慢了
没必要升级那些
你会比其他情况下更早陷入电力危机
在这一点上
消耗电力的主要是EBF和你们刚刚建立的矿石加工线
用你所有的燃料来维持它们的运转
如果你有多余的，为你的工作室供电
如果没有，这是一个很好的时机来利用您的旧蒸汽基础设施
并为您的手动机器的电池发送一滴电力
必须等待电池充电才能使用单块有点烦人
但是浪费时间重做EBF失败的冶炼操作更糟糕
如果你发现自己等得太久了
是时候扩大你的电力生产了
如果你的力量还不错
直接去洁净室
但不管怎样你都想知道接下来会发生什么
如果你用石油换能源
坦白说即使你没有
你可能会考虑一个石油钻机
和一些长距离管道
用你的探矿者在基岩上
找到一个普通油的液体池
地下水池很大
所以你在这里抽很长一段时间应该是安全的
弹出多块石油钻机
连接长距离管道输入
加载块
把管子放下直到你们回到基地
当你回来的时候
把油送入你的新蒸馏塔
这个多块有很多配置选项
弄清楚你需要哪一个
你需要知道你用的是哪个食谱
从蒸馏开始
您可以在MV下蒸馏油，提供四个输出
正如工具提示所暗示的那样
每层只能有一个流体输出
并且项目输出需要在底层
所以塔需要有五个街区高
很容易对吧
就像单块一样
输出被硫污染了
你必须把它们和氢气混合才能得到干净的输出
如果您使用具有五个输入舱口的多块化学反应器
每个油产品一个，氢气一个
和两个输出舱口
您可以在一台机器中轻松脱硫所有东西
你可能需要专门的制氢设备
并且一定要保存硫化氢以后变成硫酸
你很快就会需要每一滴你能拿到的东西
一旦你得到干净的输出
是时候决定怎么处理它们了
以下是我建议的起点
将轻质燃料和重质燃料混合得到柴油
你要么只是得到了一个补充燃料源
或者您升级了现有的
将石脑油送入多块油裂解器
轻轻蒸一下就裂了
然后把它送入最大尺寸的蒸馏塔
12个高大的庞然大物，有11个流体输出
和超级坦克的一切
每一种化学物质都是有用的
有些很快就会很关键。
至于炼厂气
你也可以蒸开裂，然后在6米高的塔里蒸馏。
但目前
如果您只想使用单块酒厂
并制造乙烯以使您的聚乙烯设置更好一点
我不会生你的气
你还可以从石脑油中提取乙烯
所以你应该都准备好了。
如果你选择所有的单块
除了饼干和蒸馏塔
一旦你完成整条线，它就会看起来像这样。
把燃料变成十六烷增压柴油
一团糟，对吧？
让我们回到LCR。
你要做很多这样的东西
所以没有像现在这样的时间开始使用它们
你需要HV层塑料
聚四氟乙烯
这是任务书中的一个小资源检查
你需要足够的氟和氯
这两种气体都不像标准气体那样容易获得
如果你没有接触过蜜蜂或IC2作物
最好的办法是电解冰晶石生成氟电解盐生成氯
好消息是
你现在真的只需要LCR的这些东西。
你想马上进入这些的主要原因
你可以将多种液体注入其中进行反应
没错，不再有细胞管理
至少对化学反应堆来说
诸神欢喜
这些东西可以容纳成吨的输入和输出舱口
并且可以过滤输出
记住记住菜谱层
并聪明地知道你提供了多少电力
接下来，你可以开始煮一些新的肉了
得到磷
你可以分解磷酸三钙
上界磷灰石脉可采
EBF中也需要氮气
你可以从细胞循环压缩空气细胞到离心机中
再一次
这是一个很长的气味
幸好你刚升级了燃料
这些不是硬性要求
除了完成任务
但就像其他电路组件一样
您的资源走得越远，输入越好
当冰球烹饪时
是时候开始准备无尘室了
任务书很好地解释了它是如何工作的
所以简单总结一下
建一个5乘5乘5的盒子
将控制器放在顶部中间
用过滤机外壳包围它
剩下的用塑胶块做
扔下LV能源舱口
维修舱口
还有一条进去的路
你最不需要的就是电缆二极管
4安培MV二极管开始时工作正常
把二极管插在墙上
并运行适量的功率
正如任务书所暗示的那样
你需要给洁净室每滴答40欧盟
所以两个低压发电机就可以了
你可能还记得和EBF打交道
能量舱口可以承受2安培的能量
所以从双方都开始供电
别忘了把电源也送到二极管里。
做一些维护
然后突然出现并打开清洁剂
如果一切顺利
你会看到它开始工作了
一次非常缓慢地提高百分之一的效率
任何低于100%效率的东西
你可能会使商品无效。
如果它碰巧是一个主机电路
你会过得很糟糕的
打开无尘室的门会降低效率
所以用电梯或旅行锚代替它
假装你从未成功过
从二极管运行一些电缆
并放下切割机、激光雕刻机和电路组装机
无尘室很快就需要高压电源了
但目前
你在玩游戏
如果你发现氯足以得到聚四氟乙烯
希望你有一些备用的大量三氯化铁
上一集你能把电路板移开
但现在不是了
除了氯
你将使用你见过的改装版《我的世界》所需的最疯狂数量的铜
至少到目前为止
一定要使用你能负担得起的最好的食谱
如果你认为你有足够的电路供应
你不知道
可能需要一整天才能在这里积累足够的东西
从八叠木板开始
但在那之后还要准备好八个
电路数量即将爆炸
制造任务所需的单一静脉注射主机
你需要14块塑料板
它从这里迅速升级
好的一面是
您现在只需一步即可制作ULV、LV和MV电路
而且尽可能便宜
储备LV电路
你会需要它们的
一旦你到了电动汽车赛道
顺便说一句，蓝色合金螺栓使用流体提取器、流体凝固器组合
你会感谢你自己的
你可以做真空冰箱
你应该优先做的事
不再有愚蠢的冷却液冷却
也没有更好的时机了
因为你刚刚意识到那些便宜的电路元件有多重要
你想和你闪亮的新矿工一起烹饪大量你刚刚从地狱中提取的钽
因此，添加一个高压二极管、一个高压发生器和高压电路汇编器
做你的第一次静脉注射
天哪，它们太贵了。
把美国航天局也变成工作台
拥有它会让你感觉很好
无论多么短暂
你现在也可以拿内爆压缩机了
在这一点上一个简单的工艺
问题是你需要炸药
我要把这作为另一个机会来鼓励人们研究蜜蜂。
因为没有它们，保持iTNT的供应会有点复杂。
Aditya蜜蜂指南的另一个无耻插头
看着他们，利用他们
尊重他们
以防你一点都不感兴趣
这是你的选择
氢气、氧气和氮气的更多设置
被用来制造氨
氮氧化物
二氧化氮
然后是硝酸
现在容易集中液体还为时过早
但十六烷柴油还需要这些化学物质
所以记住这一点
如果你聪明的话，你至少可以分享这个设置。
如果你把硫酸从油管里的硫化氢中混合
在这里放点然后和硝酸混合
否则从你的局部设施中转移一些氧气
并在现场混合一些新鲜的与硝酸混合制成硝化混合物
使用LCR配方，更容易
你从蒸馏石脑油中得到甲苯
所以通过液体灭菌器中的球形模具发送凝胶甲苯
如果你准备好了
使用糖和聚乙烯可以获得更好的甲苯回报
但是你最后一次检查你的农场是什么时候？
蜜蜂现在看起来真的那么糟糕吗？
从这里开始没有任何好转
相信我。
在你有几十堆iTNT之后
你可以做压缩板
你要在这里使用大量的资源
如果你遵从上帝的命令
这代表了日复一日的努力、冶炼和制作
视频很时髦
但不要误以为进展很快
像往常一样，任务书在布置步骤方面做得很好
你需要这里的大部分东西
缓慢而坚定地走向火箭
1层着陆器
氧气装置
和发射设备
当你拥有一切
你得给野兽加气
你有两个选择
十六烷增压柴油或RP1火箭燃料
如果你跟得紧十六烷会很容易
硝酸和硫酸准备用来制造TNT炸药
和蒸馏石脑油中的额外乙烯
你可以和氧气混合制醋酸
你需要得到乙酮的最后一种化学物质
一旦和硝酸发生反应就会变成四硝基甲烷
把它和一点燃料混合在一起
你已经准备好进行太空飞行了
如果你能自动化整个过程
这对你的基地来说也是一个相当大的升级
把那个太空装备挂起来
现在是最后检查的时候了
并确保你做到了。
继续补充你的氧气
你会注意到星系的方块是侧面的
所以要确保能量真的进去了。
氧气实际上是从收集器上流出来的。
两者都在压缩机上。
愚蠢的小积木
别忘了带上它们。
然后它确认：
氧气、坦克、矿工、压缩箱、发电机、燃料、树叶、燃料装载机、荧光灯、EnderIO电容器和能量管道
检查检查检查
你也可以在月球上收集氧气
所以你带了一堆树叶来
只是凿出一个洞穴
用树叶把它们排成一行
把收集器扑通一声放下
附近的叶子越多越好
有了这个
你准备好发射了
别忘了什么
任务控制
这是flycorand（？）
我们有影响力
没时间浪费了
如果你需要的话，杀死怪物，照亮夜晚
否则就开始勘探工作
四处寻找地牢入口
基本上只是地上的一个大洞
你可以看到它底部的砖块
你要找钕铝土矿钛铁矿铬铁矿和铝
成吨的好东西供应地球上的生命
让你的矿工出来。让他们准备好，让他们装大块。
然后去找老板
即使你不会飞
你真的可以直接穿过地牢直接进入老板竞技场
并且非常非常容易地杀死老板
拿钥匙检查箱子
为2层火箭模板祈祷吧
诶
如果你没有得到一个
找到更多的地牢，杀死更多的老板，直到你找到
不会花很长时间的
一旦你对你的收获满意了，就回家吧
也不要为在月球上安家而难过
没人评判你因为没人知道是你干的
现在剩下的一切
将铝酸盐和铝土矿加工成金红石
全力提高产量在这里是值得的
所以浸渍铝土矿以压碎形式
然后用过硫酸钠进行化学清洗
您可以通过将纯化的箱石加工成箱石浆液来扩展这一点
并投资整个铝土矿生产线
我们现在不打算掩盖它，但是查一下
疯狂的回报，疯狂
你也可以用钛铁矿做一些类似的事情
除了用硫酸
金红石的疯狂回报
和一个回收硫酸的闭环
但要等到EV
如果你绝望了
你可以把钛铁矿穿过整个
macerator-washer-macerator-centrifuge线
为了一些额外的金红石
但你最好还是多买点铝土矿
一旦你们都准备好吃金红石
你可以把它变成钛合金
任务书解释了这一点
但总而言之
整个生产线是一个巨大的闭环
唯一的输入是金红石
启动它
你需要氯和碳来搭配LCR中的金红石
电解产生的一氧化碳
把氯化钛和镁一起送到EBF
冷却生成的热钛
然后把氯化镁送入化学反应器与钠反应生成镁
还有一些盐，你可以电解成你刚刚使用的氯和钠
只需要一点物流
只要你保持金红石状态，它就可以运行
你会想经营很长一段时间
你已经做到了
你出局了
你正式不再是初学者了
正好赶上新的开始
这毕竟是GTNH
学习永远不会完成
高压也有很多事情要做
但你现在知道怎么环顾四周了
应用能源学即将面世
如果你能得到足够的钛，那就是
希望本指南能为您提供足够的信息，让您真正尝试一下
你不会后悔的
游戏里见
嘿，在外面保持积极